Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Images created by WSU-Prosser staff, 1919-1969
  - Subseries 1: Dated images, 1919-1969
    - Othello Road Sign. Sign says "Warden, WSU Research Unit". 4x5 neg. No print. 1964-07 (Box 7, Item 64.010)
    - CBRU #2. July 64. House - Roza Unit?. 4x5 neg.; print. 1964-07 (Box 7, Item 64.011)
    - CBRU #2. July 64. 4x5 neg.; print. 1964-07 (Box 7, Item 64.012)
    - No. 9. Hamilton Lab Dedication Brochure 1964. 4x5 negative is of two men working on equipment; no print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.014)
    - No. 10. Hamilton Lab Dedication, 1964. Wrong negative in envelope. 4x5 negative is of boiler room; no print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.015)
    - No. 11, 1964. Boiler Room. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.016)
    - No. 17, 1964. Fed. Prosser. Bob Early. Man in lab. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP314. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.017)
    - No. 18, 1964. Hamilton Hall foyer with two people. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP315. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.018)
    - No. 19, 1964. Hamilton Hall receptionist's desk with receptionist and two men. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP316. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.019)
    - No. 22, 1964. Clore. Walt Clore at his desk. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP317. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.020)
    - No. 24. H.P. Singleton. H.P. Singleton at desk, on phone. In Hamilton Hall?. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP318. 1964-07-08 (Box 7, Item 64.021)
    - No. 25, 1964. Hamilton Hall from SW. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.022)
    - No. 28, 1964. Hamilton Hall floor plan. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.023)
    - No. 29, 1964. Hamilton Hall floor plan. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.024)
    - No. 30, 1964. Hamilton Hall from NE with cars in lot. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP319. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.025)
    - No. 32, H.R.H. Lab. 7/6/64. Hamilton Hall, Inside hallway. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964-07-06 (Box 7, Item 64.026)
    - No. 33, 1964. Hamilton Hall, Inside Hallway, N. hall in Lab part of building. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.027)
    - No. 36, 1964. Hamilton Hall, Inside hallway, south side. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.028)
    - No. 37. 1964. Hamilton Hall from SE. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.029)
    - No. 3. Prosser Irrigation Experiment Station. Hamilton Hall, main entry. 4x5 neg. No print. 1964 (Box 7, Item 64.103)
    - Foreign Students. Seven people in photo. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP320. 1969-03-30 (Box 7, Item 69.001)
    - Fistulated Steers in field with esophogall fistulas. Koenig. 4x5 neg. No print. 1969 (Box 7, Item 69.002)
    - Matsui and asparagus. 50th Ann. IAREC. Man in lab. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP321. 1969 (Box 7, Item 69.003)
    - Wang Calculator. Woman working at computer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1969 (Box 7, Item 69.004)
    - Wang Calculator. Woman working at computer. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP322. 1969 (Box 7, Item 69.005)
    - Sprinkler irrigation on alfalfa - Kiona. One print not of this 4x5 negative. 1969 (Box 7, Item 69.006)
  - Subseries 1.2: Undated WSU-Prosser Photographs
    - Written on back of prints: (1) Second year Elberta trees on new Roza land of the Irrigation Experiment Statin, Prosser, Wash. (2) No. 7. Alfalfa and peach orchard on new Roza land. Irrigation Exp. Sta. Prosser, Wash. Rosa (sic) land first of a joint publi (Box 7, Item 0.001)
    - Nothing written on envelope. In 1936 area of file drawer. 3 3.5x5.5 negs. 19xx (Box 7, Item 0.002)
    - No date or description. Man standing in field. Potatoes?. 3.5x5.5 neg. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.010)
    - No date or description. Man standing next to hay stack. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP001. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.020)
    - No date or description. Man standing in Wheat(?) Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP002. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.030)
    - No date or description. Object (bag?) in wheat(?) field. 3.5x5.5 neg. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.040)
    - No date or description. Canal bank?. 3.5x5.5 neg. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.050)
    - No date or description. Man standing in wheat(?) field. 3.5x5.5 neg. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.060)
    - No date or description. Man standing by a plow in barnyard. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. WSUP003. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.070)
    - No date or description. Stacking Hay. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP004. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.080)
    - No date or description. Man with work Horse. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP005. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.090)
    - No date or description. Man crouching next to potatoes(?). 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP006. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.100)
    - No date or description. Man with pitchfork standing in field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP007. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.110)
    - No date or description. Man standing in potato (?) field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP008. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.120)
    - No date or description. Wheat field. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.130)
    - No date or description. Man measuring potato(?). 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. WSUP009. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.140)
    - No date or description. Figures, Maps, one photo of a grosth chamber?. No negatives. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.150)
    - Hamilton Hall. Photo taken from SE. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.161)
    - No date, no description. Hamilton Hall from east. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.162)
    - C.T.'s (?) and McPhail Traps. Frick. 5 4x5 negs. No prints. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.190)
    - Cage - Pupa; cans and Sampling Equipment. Frick. 3 prints - 2 of same thing. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.191)
    - Cage - Pupal cans and Sampling Equipment. Frick. 7 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP323. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.192)
    - Graphs. Frick. 8 4x5 negatives; no prints. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.193)
    - Pictures of Dawson's Bean and weed plots taken with various filters. No negatives. Same scene in all photos. Filter, shutter speed and f stop on card in envelope. Filed with other photos from 1958. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.210)
    - 3. None. Probably no filter. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.211)
    - 4. K2, f22. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.212)
    - 9. X1, f22. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.213)
    - 10. X1, f16. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.214)
    - 17. A. f16. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.215)
    - 18. A 1/50, f11. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.216)
    - Larvae and Pollen ball. Alkali Bee. Copy from color slide. 4x5 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.217)
    - Pollen Ball and Egg. Alkali Bee. Copy from color slide. 4x5 neg.; print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.218)
    - Copy of Slide. Alkali Bee Eggs, Larva and Pollen Ball. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.219)
    - 12 prints of insect larvae. Prints not in an envelope. Some technical data written on the back of some prints. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.220)
    - Copy from slides. Skunk Damage to alkali Bee Site. Probably 1958 when other skunk damage photos were taken. 4x5 neg.; print. 195x (Box 7, Item 1.221)
    - Copy of Slide. Skunk Damage to Alkali Bee Site, Place? Date?. Probably 1958 when other skunk damage photos were taken. 4x5 neg.; print. 195x (Box 7, Item 1.222)
    - No title, no date. Alkali bee nest in soil cross section. Filed with '56, '58, and '59 negatives. 4x5 negs. No prints. 195x (Box 7, Item 1.223)
    - Conopid fly and pupa. Copy form color slide. 4x5 neg.; print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.224)
    - No title, no date. Tiger beetle. 3.75x4 neg. No print. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.225)
    - Bee, Beefly, Sand Bee, No Name Plates. 6 4x5 negatives; no prints. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.226)
    - No title, no date. Insects and a plot map. 2 4x5 negatives and 4 5x7 negatives. No prints. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.227)
    - Cards arranged for showing field of focus at large aperature opening (a) and (b) and small opening (c). 3 4x5 negs. Prints. 19xx (Box 7, Item 1.228)
- Series 2: USDA Photographs, 1946-1952
  - 3(H) Potatoes. Hermiston, OR. B-6. 5x7 neg. 1946-07-02 (Box 8, Item 46.001)
  - 3(H) Potatoes. Hermiston, OR C-1-11. 5x7 neg. 1946-07-02 (Box 8, Item 46.002)
  - 3(H) Potatoes. Hermiston, OR C-1-12. 5x7 neg. 1946-07-02 (Box 8, Item 46.003)
  - 13(P) Sudan grass 4Q and 80# N. Prosser. 5x7 neg. 1946-09-27 (Box 8, Item 46.004)
  - 13(P) Sudan grass vs. Soybeans. Prosser. 5x7 neg. 1946-09-27 (Box 8, Item 46.005)
  - 7(H) Plot 40# N. Hermiston, OR. 5x7 neg. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.006)
  - 7(H) Corn. Hermiston, OR. 5x7 neg. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.007)
  - 7(H) Corn. Hermiston, OR. 5x7 neg. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.008)
  - 11(H). Hermiston, OR. 5x7 neg. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.009)
  - 7(H). Hermiston, OR. 5x7 neg. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.010)
  - Menzies - Potato early dying--soil sterilization exp. Check unsterilized, no fertilizer. Sagemoor and Roza soil. 2 5x7 negs.; prints. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.011)
  - Menzies - Potato early dying--soil sterilization exp. Steamed, no fertilizer. 2 5x7 negs. No prints. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.012)
  - Menzies - Potato early dying--soil sterilization exp. Sterilized NPK. 5x7 neg.; print. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.013)
  - Menzies - Potato early dying--soil sterilization exp. Sterilized NPK. 5x7 neg. 1946 (Box 8, Item 46.014)
  - General view. Flood plot-left. Winter leached-right. Border between. Elliot Farm. 5x7 neg.; print. 1947-03-01 (Box 8, Item 47.001)
  - Flood irrigation. Elliot Farm. 5x7 neg.; print. 1947-03-01 (Box 8, Item 47.002)
  - Furrow Irrigation. Winter leaching furrows. Salt crust on top of ridges. Elliot Farm - Experiment 29. 5x7 neg.; print. 1947-03-01 (Box 8, Item 47.003)
  - Exp.29©. Rep. II Ib. Down row-left. Winter leached and furrow leached. Elliot Farm. 5x7 neg.; print. 1947-04-25 (Box 8, Item 47.006)
  - Exp.29©. Rep. IV Ub. Beets in edge of salt crust. Unleached (winter) and furrow leached. Elliot Farm. 5x7 neg.; print. 1947-04-25 (Box 8, Item 47.007)
  - Rotation plot 410. 2. beets. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1947-11-12 (Box 8, Item 47.009)
  - All Fertilizer Plots #511 - sugar beets. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1947-11-12 (Box 8, Item 47.010)
  - Check vs. N160 - P120. Plot 511. Beets. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1947-11-12 (Box 8, Item 47.011)
  - Check vs. 2+7 yr. Rotation 29B and 71B. Plot 410. Beets. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1947-11-12 (Box 8, Item 47.012)
  - N160 - P120 vs. Check Rot. 29B. Plot 410. Beets. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1947-11-12 (Box 8, Item 47.013)
  - Corn. Rotation 71 Ck. vs N160 - P120 - Nelson. Back Agr. Bldg. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1947-12-01 (Box 8, Item 47.014)
  - Check N80 - P60. Corn. Rotation 73. Nelson. Back Agr. Bldg. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1947-12-01 (Box 8, Item 47.015)
  - Rot. 73 Ck. vs. Rot. 71 Ck. - Corn. Back Agr. Bldg. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1947-12-01 (Box 8, Item 47.016)
  - Corn smut charts illustrating data by Stanberry and Menzies on effect of smut on yield. 5x7 neg.; print. 1947 (Box 8, Item 47.017)
  - Furrow leaching plots. Furrows beside rows of beets. Hadley Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948 (Box 8, Item 48.001)
  - Vetch on the Moses Lake Farm. Moses Lake. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-04-01 (Box 8, Item 48.004)
  - Orchard Planting at Moses Lake. Moses Lake. 2 men planting. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP334. 1948-04-01 (Box 8, Item 48.005)
  - Cereal Nursery. Moses Lake. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-04-01 (Box 8, Item 48.006)
  - Soil crusher rolls. 5 different 4.75x3.75 negatives of soil crusher. WSUP335. 1948 (Box 8, Item 48.007)
  - Planting beets - March 1948. Elliot Farm - Toppenish. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948 (Box 8, Item 48.008)
  - Corn - Moses Lake. Moses Lake. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1948 (Box 8, Item 48.009)
  - Furrow Leaching Plots, Furrows beside rows on Hadley Farm - 1948. Hadley Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948 (Box 8, Item 48.010)
  - Rep. A 23 (P) - Peas, Prosser, WA. Prosser, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-05-14 (Box 8, Item 48.012)
  - Rep. A 23 (P) - Vetch, Prosser, WA. Prosser, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP336. 1948-05-14 (Box 8, Item 48.013)
  - Exp. 7 (G) - Corn. Greenhouse, Prosser, WA. Prosser, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-10-15 (Box 8, Item 48.014)
  - Exp. 7 (G) - Corn. Greenhouse, Prosser, WA. Prosser, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-10-15 (Box 8, Item 48.015)
  - Hop yard. Charvet's. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-04-22 (Box 8, Item 48.016)
  - Yakima Chief Hop Yard with peas. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-04-15 (Box 8, Item 48.017)
  - R. Charvet's Hop Yard with Vetch plots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-04-22 (Box 8, Item 48.018)
  - Potato - Mosaic symptoms on Var. Glenmeer. Menzies. 1 healthy and 2 diseased shoots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-09 (Box 8, Item 48.019)
  - Potato - plants in Exp. G-8 (Viets), Exp. F (Menzies) replanting. A- normal Roza soil (Pot 26), B-Childs soil plus several zinc treatments (Pot 38), C-Childs soil untreated(Pot 33). 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948 (Box 8, Item 48.020)
  - Asparagus Crown Rot. Inocculated tests. Irrig. Exp. Sta. Bottom - roots inoculated by pin pricks, lateral cuts and bruising, respectively from L to R. Top row- Ck. uninocul. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-05 (Box 8, Item 48.021)
  - Asparagus Crown Rot. Inocculated tests. Irrig. Exp. Sta. Top row -inoculation with penicillium culture. Bottom row- Ck. shows some pathogens. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-05 (Box 8, Item 48.022)
  - Potato-producing seedlings for transplanting to field for leaf roll resistance tests. Each flat separate cross. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-06 (Box 8, Item 48.023)
  - Potato production of seedlings for leafroll resistance test. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-06 (Box 8, Item 48.024)
  - Potato - "fern leaf". Netted Gem variety. Showing leaf distortion. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-08 (Box 8, Item 48.025)
  - Potato "fern leaf".Condition associated with leveled areas on Roza project. Shoots show several stages in severity. A physiologic disorder?. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-09 (Box 8, Item 48.026)
  - Potato "fern leaf"mild symptoms illustrating reduced terminal leaf growth. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-09 (Box 8, Item 48.027)
  - Potato-Leafroll seedling plants in test plots. Irrig. Exp. Sta. Small plant in foreground illustrates current-season symptoms in comparison with healthy plant on right. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-09 (Box 8, Item 48.029)
  - Potato-leafroll resistance test plots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-09 (Box 8, Item 48.030)
  - Sugar beet - top symptoms of verticillium wilt on plants collected in the Sunnyside area. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-10 (Box 8, Item 48.031)
  - Sugar beet verticillium wilt. Plant on left is healthy. Specimens from rotation plots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-10 (Box 8, Item 48.032)
  - Sugar beet verticillium wilt. Shows internal discolorations associated with infection. Rotation plots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-11 (Box 8, Item 48.033)
  - Sugar beet verticillium wilt. Section of roots to show internal discolorations. Root in center is healthy. Rotation plots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1948-11 (Box 8, Item 48.034)
  - Farmer spraying wheat. West of Connell. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-04-29 (Box 8, Item 49.001)
  - Cheat grass sod on the Winchester Farm. Winchester Farm. 4 4.75x3.75 negs.; 4 prints. 1949-04-28 (Box 8, Item 49.002)
  - Zn sprayed tow on left. Corn. Pasco, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-08-30 (Box 8, Item 49.004)
  - Zn deficient corn plant. Pasco, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-08-30 (Box 8, Item 49.005)
  - High yield corn exp. 960# plot. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP337. 1949-08-30 (Box 8, Item 49.006)
  - High yield corn experiment. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP338. 1949-08-30 (Box 8, Item 49.007)
  - High yield corn experiment. 960# N plot. Pasco, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-08-30 (Box 8, Item 49.008)
  - Zn deficient corn plants. Idahybrid 544. R. Moe's - Pasco Slope, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09-30 (Box 8, Item 49.009)
  - Check row in center. Zn sprayed row on left. Corn. R. Moe's - Pasco Slope, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09-30 (Box 8, Item 49.010)
  - Check row in center. Zn sprayed row on left. Corn. R. Moe's - Pasco Slope, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP339. 1949-09-30 (Box 8, Item 49.012)
  - Zn deficient corn plant, Idahybrid 544. R. Moe's - Pasco Slope, WA. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09-30 (Box 8, Item 49.013)
  - Potato scab - lime experiment in greenhouse No. G.P.I. second crop. Representative tubers from the following treatments:1. Check, 3.CaO -1.4tons, 4.CaO-2.8 tons, 5.CaO-5.6tons. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949 (Box 8, Item 49.014)
  - Potato scab-control in fold by use of sulpher. Richens Farm, Moses Lake, treatments made April 1948. Photo shows results on 2nd crop-1949. Top l.to.r. Check, 500# S, 1000# S, 2000# S. 2500# S. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949 (Box 8, Item 49.015)
  - Potato - Chronic leafroll from Minnesota seed. Greenhouse grown. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-03-30 (Box 8, Item 49.021)
  - Potato - Chronic leafroll in Netted Gem grown in greenhouse, seed from Moses Lake. (Unit 17 of Expt. G. 1948-49.). 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-03-30 (Box 8, Item 49.022)
  - Potato scab respresentative tubers from greenhouse experiment H-1948-49. Shows control of scab by high rates of CaO (No.3, 4, 5) and no control from equivalent rates of CaSO₄ and no control from equivalent rates of CaSO₄ and Na₂CO₃. No.1 is check. 4.75x3. (Box 8, Item 49.023)
  - Vetch - root rot winter injury showing killing of shoots and lesions on top root. (Rhizoctonia?). 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-04-07 (Box 8, Item 49.024)
  - Vetch - winter injury root rot showing rotting of top root and wilting of top. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-04-07 (Box 8, Item 49.025)
  - Vetch - healthy for comparison with root rot photos. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-04-07 (Box 8, Item 49.026)
  - Vetch - lesions (Rhizoctonia?) on new shoots. Part of root-rot winter-injury complex. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-04-07 (Box 8, Item 49.027)
  - Vetch - healthy for comparison with diseased plants. Note abundant nodulations and healthy shoots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-04-07 (Box 8, Item 49.028)
  - Vetch-root rot - winter injury. Showing killing of new shoots at point of seed attachment. Irrigatiion Experiment Station - Roza Unit. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-04-07 (Box 8, Item 49.029)
  - Vetch-root rot - winter injury showing killing of shoots and cankering of top root. Irrigatiion Experiment Station - Roza Unit. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-04-07 (Box 8, Item 49.030)
  - Potato-scab experiments. Effects of gypsum. Potato-scab - field samples from test showing lack of beneti from soil Sulfaid (gypsum and sulphur). Two lots top to bottom - check, 1500# sulfaid/ac., 3000# sulfaid/ac. Moses Lake 1949. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1 (Box 8, Item 49.031)
  - Potato seed - experiment on control by means of lime materials experiment G.P.Z. Potato scab. Control by means of lime in greenhouse Experiment G.P.I. second planting harvest September 1949. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.032)
  - Potato--early dying soil fumigation experiment 1949. Treatment, check + 40# N.leafroll resistance test plots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.033)
  - Potato--early dying soil fumigation experiment 1949. Treatment, DD + 40# N/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.034)
  - Potato--fernleaf--field symptoms: 1.General view of affected spot. 2. Closeup of plants. 2 4.75x3.75 negs. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.035)
  - Potato--early dying soil sumigation experiment 1949. Treatment DD plus 160# N/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.036)
  - Potato scab--Lime equipment G.P.F. second crop. 7 - CaSO₄, 2H₂O - 4.3 T/ac., 12 Na₂CO₃ - 2.7 T/ac. Rotation plots. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.037)
  - Potato - early dying. Soil fumigation expt. Treatment Check + 160# N/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.038)
  - Potato - early dying. Soil fumigation expt. Treatment Chloropicrin + 120# N/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.039)
  - Potato - early dying. Soil fumigation expt. Treatment Chloropicrin + 40# N/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.040)
  - Potato - early dying. Soil fumigation expt. Treatment E.D.B.+ 160# N/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.041)
  - Potato - early dying. Soil fumigation expt. Treatment E.D.B.+ 40# N/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.042)
  - Potato - fern leaf symptoms on Netted Gem in field. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-09 (Box 8, Item 49.043)
  - Potato green dwarf? Seed tubers at harvest time showing multiple shoot development and failure to shoot above ground. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-10 (Box 8, Item 49.044)
  - Potato - scab on variety. WhiteRose from Moses Lake area. Shows a russetting that seems to be due to scab in contrast to nonscabby potatoes. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-10 (Box 8, Item 49.045)
  - Potato - seed pieces taken from seedling field test at harvest time showing dormancy. Tissue is very firm. May be same as bunch top disease (purple top). 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-10 (Box 8, Item 49.046)
  - Potato - seed pieces taken from seedling field test at harvest time showing stunted shoots or dormant eyes. Seed pieces are very hard, may be the same as bunch top described by MacLeod in New Brunswick. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-10 (Box 8, Item 49.047)
  - Tomato - dwarf from potato by grafting. Left- healthy, Right- affected. Grafted August, 1949. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-11 (Box 8, Item 49.048)
  - Tomato - big bud. From potato. Close-up showing inflated calyx. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-11 (Box 8, Item 49.049)
  - Tomato - dwarf from potato by grafting. Grafted August, 1949. Plant on right is not entirely dead by axillary shoots are severely stunted. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-11 (Box 8, Item 49.050)
  - Tomato - "Dwarf" induced by budding from "greendwarf" potato seedling from field. Grafted Aug. 1949. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-11 (Box 8, Item 49.051)
  - Tomato - big bud - from potato by grafting. Close-up showing terminal growth modification and abnormal infloresence. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-11 (Box 8, Item 49.052)
  - Tomato - Big Bud induced by grafting from "greendwarf"potato seedlings from field. Grafted Aug.'49. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-11 (Box 8, Item 49.053)
  - Tomato - big bud. Leaf symptoms of big-bud induced on tomato by grafting from potato seedling presumably infected with green dwarf. Plant on right is healthy. Note marginal chlorosis of leaflets and leaf malformations induced by this virus. 4.75x3.75 neg. (Box 8, Item 49.054)
  - Tomato - big bud. Symptoms of Stokesdale tomato induced by grafting from potato seedling presumably infected with green dwarf. Terminal growth is dwarfed, leaf size reduced and newest growth is chloratic, in fact, it looks etiolated. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1949-1 (Box 8, Item 49.055)
  - Tomato - big bud. Symptoms of Stokesdale tomato induced by grafting from potato seedling presumably infected with green dwarf. Picture shows various types of malformation of inflorescence. Tree with fruit was the lowest one to bear following grafting. Lar (Box 8, Item 49.056)
  - Tomato - big bud. Symptoms of Stokesdale tomato induced by grafting from potato seedling presumably infected with green dwarf. Shoot on left is healthy, that on right from grafted plant. Note stunting leaf chlorosis and malformation of flower parts. 4.75x (Box 8, Item 49.057)
  - Experiment G-18. Plot 20 Sagemoor 9-6", Plot 14 Timmerman 22-36", Plot 17 Timmerman 22-36" (leached). 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949-12 (Box 8, Item 49.058)
  - Profile of Ephrata fine sandy loam. Moses Lake Development Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1949 (Box 8, Item 49.059)
  - 1950 hop selections. Hop yard - Irrigation Experiment Station. 5x7 neg. 1950-08-15 (Box 8, Item 50.001)
  - 1950 hop selections. Hop yard - Irrigation Experiment Station. 5x7 neg. 1950-08-15 (Box 8, Item 50.002)
  - 1950 hop selections. Hop yard - Irrigation Experiment Station. 5x7 neg. 1950-08-15 (Box 8, Item 50.003)
  - 1950 hop selections. Hop yard - Irrigation Experiment Station. 5x7 neg. 1950-08-15 (Box 8, Item 50.004)
  - 1950 hop selections. Hop yard - Irrigation Experiment Station. 5x7 neg. 1950-08-15 (Box 8, Item 50.005)